<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tatsu Online</title>
    <link>https://tatsuonline.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tatsu Online</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tatsuonline.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Censorship in the Marketplace of Ideas</title>
      <link>https://tatsuonline.github.io/posts/adpocalypse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tatsuonline.github.io/posts/adpocalypse/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Over the last few years, the online video-sharing platform YouTube has been subject to a series of policy changes that have had a profound effect on the type of content and the types of ideas that are expressed or discussed by creators on the platform. Through examples and comparisons, I will attempt to argue that YouTube has fallen prey to the same fiscal compulsions that led to the censorship of printed media in the United States during its &amp;ldquo;golden era&amp;rdquo; of the early nineteenth century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The EARN IT Act</title>
      <link>https://tatsuonline.github.io/posts/earn-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tatsuonline.github.io/posts/earn-it/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Earlier this month, United States Senators Lindsey Graham and Richard Blumenthal introduced a bill on the floor, the so-called EARN IT Act. The title of the bill is a backronym which spells out &amp;ldquo;E liminating A busive and R ampant N eglect of I nteractive T echnologies&amp;rdquo;. The purported goal of this bill is to establish a National Commission on Online Child Sexual Exploitation Prevention; however, the bill also exploits the general lack of public understanding of the technology behind encryption in an effort to eliminate its use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing Maxwell&#39;s Equations</title>
      <link>https://tatsuonline.github.io/posts/maxwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tatsuonline.github.io/posts/maxwell/</guid>
      <description>Introduction There are a few times in physics when the equations describing physical phenomena are surprisingly simple and beautiful as a result. Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s equations are an excellent example of this; with just four equations, all of classical electromagnetism can be described.
In differential form1, they are as follows:
\begin{equation} \label{eq:1} \nabla \cdot E = \frac{\rho}{\varepsilon_0} \end{equation}
\begin{equation} \label{eq:2} \nabla \cdot B = 0 \end{equation}
\begin{equation} \label{eq:3} \nabla \times E = -\frac{\partial B}{\partial t} \end{equation}</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>